let questions=[
    {
        question_num: 1,
        question: "The multiple births association is having a picnic. There are 10 families going. Some families have 2 kids, some have 3 and others as many as 6. How many families have 2 kids?",
        answer: " All of them",
        options: [
            "At least Half",
            "Five Families",
            "At Most Five",
            "All of them"
        ]
    },
    {
        question_num: 2,
        question: "1.	Your parents have six sons including you and each son has one sister. How many people are in the family?",
        answer: " 9",
        options: [
            "14",
            "7",
            "9",
            "Can't say"
        ]
    },
    {
        question_num: 3,
        question: "A stamp and a postcard together cost Rs. 150. The postcard costs Rs. 100 more than the stamp. How much does the stamp cost?",
        answer: " Rs. 25",
        options: [
            "Rs. 50 ",
            "Rs. 100",
            "Rs. 25",
            "Rs. 125"
        ]
    },
    {
        question_num: 4,
        question: "Fourteen of the kids in the class are girls. Eight of the kids wear blue shirts. Two of the kids are neither girls nor wear a blue shirt. If five of the kids are girls who wear blue shirts, how many kids are in the class?",
        answer: " 19",
        options: [
            "16",
            "Rs. 100",
            "19",
            "Rs. 125"
        ]
    },
    {
        question_num: 5,
        question: "6 gardeners plant 6 trees in 6 minutes. How many gardeners will be needed to plant 60 trees in 60 minutes?",
        answer: " 6",
        options: [
            "10",
            "60",
            "15",
            "6"
        ]
    },
    {
        question_num: 6,
        question: "Which word logically comes next in this sequence? Spots, pots, opts…",
        answer: " Both A and B",
        options: [
            "tops",
            "opts",
            "Both A and B",
            "Can't say"
        ]
    },
    {
        question_num: 7,
        question: "There are 7 boxes of chocolates. If you take away 3, how many do you have? ",
        answer: " 3",
        options: [
            "3",
            "6",
            "4",
            "Not Enough",
        ]
    },
    {
        question_num: 8,
        question: "There are 7 boxes of chocolates. If you take away 3, how many do you have? ",
        answer: " 3",
        options: [
            "3",
            "6",
            "4",
            "Not Enough",
        ]
    },
    {
        question_num: 7,
        question: "The water level in a reservoir is low, but doubles every day. It takes 60 days to fill the reservoir. How long does it take for the reservoir to become half full? ",
        answer: " 59",
        options: [
            "60",
            "61",
            "30",
            "59",
        ]
    },
    {
        question_num: 9,
        question: "Barry entered his workshop at 6 o'clock. If he turned the clock upside down, which direction would the hour hand be going? ",
        answer: " 10",
        options: [
            "Downward",
            "Sideways",
            "Towards 3 o’ clock",
            "Upwards",
        ]
    },
    {
        question_num: 11,
        question: "Jill had 10 prize pigs. All but 5 died. How many does she have now?",
        answer: " 5",
        options: [
            "5",
            "10",
            "15",
            "6",
        ]
    },
    {
        question_num: 13,
        question: "You have $98 and each cup of coffee costs $3. How many coffees can you afford? ",
        answer: " 10",
        options: [
            "28",
            "30",
            "32",
            "33",
        ]
    },
]